Linqto Privacy Policy
=====================

Linqto, Inc. (referred to as **Linqto, we, us** or{‘ ‘} **our**) has implemented this Privacy Policy to provide users of our website{‘ ‘} [https://www.linqto.com](https://www.linqto.com/) ( **“Site”)** and our Mobile App/platform (**“App”**) collectively (**“Application”**) and our other services with information about how we collect, hold and use Personal Information you provide to us. If you wish to make any inquiries regarding this Privacy Policy, you should contact Linqto in any of the ways specified below.

From time to time, Linqto may be related to other entities (**Related Entities**) and a reference in this Privacy Policy to Linqto, we, us or our also refers to our Related Entities. By using our Application, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information by Linqto as explained below. In addition to the Privacy Policy, our Terms of Use and our respective Trading Rules shall apply to you and everyone else who uses this Application.

Linqto takes safeguarding online privacy seriously. Please read the following to understand Linqto’s privacy practices regarding information we collect from users of our Application (as defined in our{‘ ‘} [Terms of Use](https://www.linqto.com/terms-of-use/)). From time to time, Linqto may change this privacy policy as described in Section 13 (below).

We may, from time to time, review and update this Privacy Policy, including taking into account new laws, regulations, practices and technology. All Personal Information held by us will be governed by our then most recent Privacy Policy as published on our Application.

#### 1\. Consent.

By submitting Personal Data through our Application, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In addition the Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions of Use shall apply to you and everyone else who uses this Application. By submitting your Personal Data you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

#### 2\. A note about children.

We do not intentionally gather Personal Data about visitors who are under the age of 13.

#### 3\. A note to users outside the United States.

Your Personal Data may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in other countries, including the United States, where laws regarding processing of Personal Data may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

#### 4\. What data do we collect from you?

> (a) Data You Provide. **“Personal Data”** means data that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, as well as any other non-public information about you that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing data. We collect Personal Data from you when you create an account as described below ( **“Account”**). We also collect information from you when you use our Application as described below. When you order services, we (or our service provider) will collect all information necessary to complete the transaction. We retain information on your behalf, such as files and messages that you store using your Account. If you provide us feedback or contact us via email, we will collect your name and email address, as well as any other content included in the email, in order to send you a reply. We may also collect Personal Data, such as at other points in our Application that state that Personal Data is being collected.
> 
> (b) **Data Collected via Technology.** To make our Application more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) collect information from you, including your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session), domain name, and/or a date/time stamp for your visit. Linqto may use cookies on its Site to save users time so they do not have to enter their password each time they visit the Application. Linqto may also use cookies on its download page to speed up users’ activities during authentication. Linqto may also use cookies in other areas on its Application now and in the future. Linqto’s cookies do not contain Personal Data. “Cookies” give users a unique, random ID by storing small text files onto a user’s computer hard drive with the user’s browser. Cookies enable a web site to track a user’s activities on a web site. Users are free to change their web browsers to prevent the acceptance of cookies. Please note that if you disable Cookies, parts of our Application may not function as intended.
> 
> (c) **Google Analytics.** We currently use Google Analytics. Google Analytics collects information anonymously and reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. Google Analytics uses its own cookie to track visitor interactions. Website owners can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with their website so they can improve their website and how people find it. Please see the following links for more information about Google Analytics:{‘ ‘} [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy) .

#### 5\. Specific Information About Mobile Apps

The Mobile App may at times, and in different places, display information or require information in alternative formats from website entry or view. Each interface complies with all privacy procedures mentioned herein regardless of these differences.

#### 6\. Why does Linqto collect Personal Data, and how is it used?

> (a) a. Linqto uses your Personal Data create your Account and to operate, maintain and provide to you the general and personalized features and functionality of the Application. We may also use your information to improve our Application, provide you with service you request, to send you administrative emails, to respond to your emails, and to notify you of any other changes within the Application that may affect you. Linqto does not use your email address or other Personal Data to send commercial or marketing messages to you without your consent. If you have consented to receive commercial or marketing messages, Linqto may notify you of product upgrades and updates, new products, special offers, seminars and conventions presented through Linqto within an indicated area of interest.
> 
> (b) Linqto may use Anonymous Data you submit for purposes related to Linqto’s business, including, but not limited to, generating statistical studies, conducting market research, and improving website and app services, features and functionality. “**Anonymous Data**” means data that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Data; Anonymous Data does not, by itself, permit the identification of individual persons. We may create Anonymous Data records from Personal Data by excluding information (such as your name) that make the data personally identifiable to you. We reserve the right to use Anonymous data for any purpose and disclose Anonymous Data to third parties in its sole discretion.
> 
> (c) We use the Personal Data we collect about you for our business functions and activities, which may include the following:
> 
> > 1. {‘ ‘} To administer our relationship with you including responding to your queries;
> > 2. {‘ ‘} To confirm your identity in order to create your account and ensure that you are eligible to use the services provided on the Application;
> > 3. {‘ ‘} To conduct required Know-Your-Client (KYC), Anti-Money Laundering (AML) and Counter Terrorism and Financing (CTF) multi-jurisdictional legislation regime checks on you in connection with your use of the Application;
> > 4. {‘ ‘} To review any marketing or other information that you may make via the Application;
> > 5. {‘ ‘} To confirm that you are eligible to register an account through the Site including in accordance with relevant legislation;
> > 6. {‘ ‘} To provide services through the Application including allowing you to contact other users and account holders using the information on the Application;
> > 7. {‘ ‘} To monitor, improve and administer the Site and the services provided on the Application;
> > 8. To enable us to create a user profile to better serve you;
> > 9. {‘ ‘} To enable us to conduct surveys and aggregate user profiles;
> > 10. To ensure security of the Site and your user profile;
> > 11. To train our staff and provide quality assurance;
> > 12. To process any job application submitted by you;
> > 13. {‘ ‘} To enable us to comply with all our legal and regulatory obligations;
> > 14. {‘ ‘} To share your Personal Data with our Related Entities, business partners and our selected third parties;
> > 15. {‘ ‘} To contact you to ensure customer satisfaction in respect of our role as a Site provider and assist you in getting the best value from our service; and
> > 16. {\`If you are an employee or other representative of a client to which we provide our services or a supplier or service provider to us, to communicate with you about your or your employer’s engagement with us and otherwise as specified in this Privacy Policy.\`}
> 
> (d) We reserve the right at all times to monitor, review, retain, and/or disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any applicable law, but we have no obligation to monitor the use of the Site or to retain the content of any user session.
> 
> (e) In the event that we intend to enter into a major corporate transaction, such as a sale of control of our or another business, we may disclose certain of your Personal Data to potential buyers, underwriters or advisors. If we do this, we will take reasonable precautions to ensure that the recipients of your Personal Data are obligated to keep it confidential.
> 
> (f) We may, from time to time, expand, reduce or sell our business and this may involve the transfer of certain sections or the whole business to other parties. Your Personal Data will, where it is relevant to any such transaction, be transferred to the new owner or newly controlling party who will, under the terms of this Privacy Policy, be permitted to use your Personal Data for the purposes for which it was supplied by you.
> 
> (g) You consent to us using your Personal Data in the ways described in this Policy.
> 
> (h) If you do not consent to us using your Personal Data in the above ways you must not provide your Personal Data to us. You should also not provide your Personal Data to us if you are under 18 years of age. If you choose not to provide your Personal Data to us for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, we may not be able to provide you with requested products or services and access to some of the functionality of the Site.
> 
> (i) We may collect and use your Personal Data for other purposes not listed above. If we do so, we will make it known to you at the time we collect or use your Personal Data.
> 
> (j) We do not otherwise collect, use or disclose your Personal Data without your permission, unless the collection, use or disclosure is:
> 
> * {‘ ‘} In accordance with this Privacy Policy or any agreement you enter into with us; or
> * {‘ ‘} Required or authorized by law, including without limitation the relevant multi-jurisdictional Privacy principles.
> 
> (k) Access to certain content on our Application may be allowed under a written agreement between you and Linqto and will require a username and/or password. In some cases, failure to provide personal information may prevent you from accessing our Application containing certain confidential information, assets, services, or promotional offers. By accessing and using our protected and secured Application, you agree to maintain the confidentiality of the username and password you selected to access our Application and consent to our Terms of Use.
> 
> (l) If you provide your consent to receiving direct marketing from our third-party business partners, we will provide them with your Personal Data to enable them to send information and advertising material to you. You can opt out of receiving this material from third parties by using the contact details specified below if you do not want to receive marketing information from us.
> 
> (m) When providing a telephone you are consenting to be contacted by SMS text message. Message & data rates may apply. Reply STOP to opt out of further messaging.

#### 7\. How do I have my personal information deactivated, changed or updated?

> (a) Linqto respects your privacy and realizes that not everyone likes to receive special offers or information. If you would like your name deactivated from Linqto’s lists, please use the contact information below to request that Linqto deactivate you from its lists. Be sure to include your name, postal address, telephone number, information contained in your Linqto mailer, and/or other necessary information requested for deactivation. Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you service related communication, including notices of any updates to our Terms of Use or Privacy Policy.
> 
> (b) If you believe that Linqto may not have your correct and current personal information, you may update your information any time [here](https://www.linqto.com/profile) or by using the contact information below to inform Linqto of changes in your personal information. You may request deletion of your Personal Data by us [here](https://www.linqto.com/settings), but please note that we may be required to maintain this information as required by federal and state laws, rules and regulations.  When we delete any information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives.

#### 8\. Does Linqto share the information that it gathers with third parties?

Linqto does not share Personal Data with third parties without your consent except as described below:

> (a) We may share your Personal Data with third party service providers to: provide you with the Application that we offer you through our Application; to conduct quality assurance testing; to facilitate creation of Accounts; to provide technical support; and/or to provide other services. These third party service providers are required not to use your Personal Data other than to provide the services requested by Linqto.
> 
> (b) We may share some or all of your Personal Data with our parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control (individually and collectively, “Affiliates”), in which case we will require our Affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy. If another company acquires our company, business, or our assets, that company will possess the Personal Data collected by it and us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.
> 
> (c) Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Data, Linqto may disclose Personal Data as may be necessary to respond to violations of the Linqto Terms of Use or Privacy Policy, to report suspected unlawful activity to law enforcement officials, governmental agencies, or other third parties, in connection with any legal investigation, to comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on Linqto, or to protect or defend the rights or property of Linqto or users of the Application (collectively, the “**Enforcement Exceptions**“).
> 
> (d) Linqto may share Anonymous Data with third parties as described in this Policy.

#### 9\. Social Networking Sites (SNS).

> If you associate your Linqto Account with your login credentials from a social networking site (e.g., Facebook) (“**SNS** “), we may receive Personal and/or Anonymous Data about you from such SNS, in accordance with the terms and conditions (e.g., terms of use and privacy policy) of the SNS (“**SNS Terms** “). If you elect to share your information with these SNS, we will share information with them in accordance with your election.
> 
> The SNS Terms of these SNS will apply to the information we disclose to them. For example, your Linqto Account is associated with your Facebook account. Facebook will provide us your basic information (which may include your name, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID, list of friends, or other information you share publicly on Facebook) as well as your email address, location, birthday and publishing stream, each in accordance with Facebook’s terms and conditions. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via the Application. In addition, you may elect to share certain content from our Application with Facebook. Once provided to Facebook, Facebook’s terms and conditions will govern its use of this information.

#### 10\. Note About Third Party Websites.

When you click on a link to any other website or location, you will leave our Site and go to another site and another entity may collect Personal Data or Anonymous Data from you. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of data after you click on links to such outside websites.

#### 11\. What is Linqto’s commitment to data security?

Linqto recognizes your concern for security, and will use reasonable efforts to establish secure connections with you and to limit access to databases containing Personal Data to authorized personnel only. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while Linqto uses reasonable efforts to protect your Personal Data, Linqto cannot guarantee its absolute security.

#### 12\. Overseas Disclosures

Some of your Personal Information may be transferred, stored, processed or used overseas by us or by third party service providers. This may happen if our Related Entities are overseas, if we outsource certain activities overseas or if transactions, information, services or products have an overseas connection. You consent to the collection, use, storage, and processing of your Personal Information outside of the USA.

#### 13\. What are Linqto’s contact procedures?

If you believe Linqto has not adhered to its privacy statement, if you would like to be deactivated from Linqto’s lists, or if you would like to update your personal information, you may notify Linqto by e-mail to support@linqto.com, or postal mail at Linqto, Inc., PO Box 1193, Pebble Beach, CA 93953. Linqto will use reasonable efforts to promptly resolve any issues.

#### 14\. What to do if you have a question, problem or complaint about our use of your personal data of this Privacy Policy

If you: i. Have a query or concern about this Privacy Policy or our Personal Information handling processes; ii. Wish to make a complaint in relation to a breach by us of your privacy; iii. Would like to access your Personal Data held by us; iv. Would like to opt out of direct marketing; or v. Would like to correct your Personal Information held by us, Please contact us as set out below. We will investigate your queries and complaints within a reasonable period of time of receiving the complaint and will notify you of the outcome of our investigation.

#### 15\. Conflicts

In the event of conflict between the provisions of this Privacy Policy, the [Terms of Use](https://www.linqto.com/terms-of-use/) or{‘ ‘} [Trading Rules](https://www.linqto.com/disclosures) and the provisions of any other documents relating to Linqto, the Application or otherwise, the provisions of the Trading Rules shall prevail.

#### 16\. How may Linqto Change this Privacy Policy?

> {‘ ‘} (a)) This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any material changes in the way we use your Personal Data, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our Application. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you or thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our Application. These changes will be effective immediately for new users of our Application. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your Personal Data to provide us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice.
> 
> {‘ ‘} (b) In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of Personal Data that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your Personal Data, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us. Continued use of our Application, following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

#### Contact Details

**Linqto, Inc.**

Address: 101 Metro Drive, Suite 335, San Jose, CA 95110  
Email: support@linqto.com

Last updated: September 2020
